abcdu.com 2017-12-26

# Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order. 

When ordering or registering, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To improve our website  
(We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.) 

• To improve customer service  
(Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.) 

• To process transactions

If you decide to opt-in to a mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

 **How do we protect your information?**  

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or login to your account.

We use a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

 **Do we use cookies?**  

Yes, cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting Model Domains support. 

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  

Upon purchasing a domain from  Model Domains, your personal information may be provided to the current registrar of record, allowing you to gain control and access to your domain name. Please note, domain name registration contact information is made public through "whois" services, and by providing information to  Model Domains means the contact information may be made public as required by the domain name registrar which maintains the domain registration. 

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**  

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

 **Terms and Conditions**  

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](http://modeldomains.com/index.php?route=information/information&information_id=5) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

 **Your Consent**  

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy. 

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**  

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 5/7/2017 

 **Contacting Us**  

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may use the [contact us](http://modeldomains.com/index.php?route=information/contact) form on this Web site.
